betphoenix.com 2010-05-23

# Privacy Policy - BetPhoenix Entertainment

BetPhoenix.com is respectful to the privacy of our visitors. By reading this Online Privacy Policy carefully you will be aware of the information we gather through this Web site and understand our privacy practices. 

### Children's Protection

BetPhoenix.com does not market to children under the age of 18. If you're under 18, please don't visit www.BetPhoenix.com. 

### What Information BetPhoenix.com Collects

BetPhoenix.com gathers the details provided by visitors upon registering or initiating transactions and tracking information from navigating BetPhoenix.com site. Sites featured on and accessed through our site may gather information as well.

Our goal is to use the information you provide us to serve your needs better. The more information you share will help us improving the quality and usefulness of our site.

We may request the following information when you make a purchase: 

  * Name
  * Email address
  * Date of birth
  * Shipping and/or billing address
  * Phone or fax number
  * Credit card number or account number
  * Social Security Number
  * Driver's license number

Some information is needed to process your purchase. The contact information is used in case we have difficulties with your order as well as providing important updates regarding your account and/or our service.

We will require your Social Security Number only as a confirmation when you inquire about accessing your credit card account. 

### Email Addresses

Occasionally we may provide via email address new offers, products, services and other useful information that we hope will interest you. In case you do not wish to receive such email, let us know upon registering your email address that you desire not to receive such information or offers. 

### Updating Your Registration Profile

You may contact the Member Services department or 1-888-238-8018 to update your contact information such as phone, account or e-mail preference information. For verification purposes we will require your Member Name and Password before making any changes to your profile. 

### Cookies

To help us tailor our site to the needs and interests of our visitors, we keep track of the pages visited by our users by placing a small entry in a text file, called a cookie, on your hard drive. The cookie contains an ID number that allows us to track the pages you've visited. We aggregate this data with data on the pages visited by other users to track overall visitor traffic patterns. We use this information to improve our site by making it more responsive to the needs of our users. The help function on most browsers contains information on how to set your browser to notify you before accepting a cookie or to disable cookies entirely. 

### Browser Level Information

Our Web server automatically collects your IP address when you request pages from our server. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers connected to the Internet to identify your computer so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you. We also collect information on the operating system you're running on your computer and the Web browser software you're using to access our site so we can optimize our site for the most popular operating systems and Web browsers. And, because we like to know how you found our site, we keep track of where you came from. 

### Pop-up Surveys

From time to time, we request information from users via pop-up surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary; if you don't want to provide the requested information, please don't respond to the survey. The information we gather through these surveys will be used to improve our site. 

### Information Collected by Third Parties

Of course, our site includes links to other Web sites, and provides access to products and services offered by third parties, whose privacy policies we don't control. When you access another Web site or purchase products or services or conduct other transactions through our Web site, use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you're visiting or the provider of such products or services. The provider's privacy practices may differ from ours. If you can't find the privacy policy of any of our provider partners via a link either from the site's page or from the pages on which the products or services are offered, you should contact the provider directly for more information. 

### Security

The information we collect from our visitors is stored in databases we control. Physical access to the servers on which we store visitor information is restricted. We use your credit card information only to bill you for the products and services you order from us. We don't share your credit card information with anyone, except as may be necessary to process your transactions. To protect the privacy of your credit card number and other ordering information, we encrypt this information for transit over the Internet using a Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") connection. However, as effective as modern security practices are, no physical or electronic security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won't be intercepted while being transmitted over the Internet.

Most Web browsers allow use of an SSL connection. If your browser does not support use of an SSL connection, or if you prefer not to send your credit card number over the Internet, you can place your order by calling us toll free at 1-888-238-8018. 

### Disclosure of Information

We may occasionally release information about our visitors if forced by law, when necessary to enforce our Visitor Agreement, or in order to protect the rights, property or safety of visitors to our site, our clients, the public or BetPhoenix.com. We may also buy or sell assets to pursue the growth of our business. Although unlikely, if another company acquires a BetPhoenix.com property or substantially all business units, all client data will be treated confidentially and won't be sold to others; information on our visitors would be among the transferred assets. 

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

This privacy policy adjusts to the evolving Web environment, thus is subject to change; at which moment the new policy will be posted immediately. The use of BetPhoenix.com and our services constitutes an agreement to solve any dispute over privacy by the then-current version of the Online Privacy Policy and Visitor Agreement. We will notify you of any changes affecting the use of personally identifiable information differently from what was stated at the time it was collected, giving you the option to decline the proposed use. 

### If you need Answers or Assistance

Member Services is at your service to answer and guidance in resolving any dispute concerning this Online Privacy Policy. Please call our representatives at 1-888-238-8018 if you have questions or complains. 

### Mobile Phone Numbers

As with email address and surveys, it is our interest to benefit you via sms with new offers as well as important products and services of high interest. Nevertheless, if you find this useful information unsuitable to your needs, let us know that you would rather not receive such messages or offers when registering a mobile phone number in our site.
